shopsimple.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - ShopSimple

Last modified on April 7, 2013.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using our website or services. By accessing or using our website or our services (other than to read this privacy policy for the first time), you agree to this Privacy Policy.

We （ShopSimple） take the privacy rights of users of the website ([http://www.shopsimple.com](http://www.shopsimple.com/)) very seriously，and we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. For ShopSimple.com, privacy is a top priority and we provide this Privacy Policy to outline our practices and procedures with respect to information collection and use, to enable you to make an informed decision about sharing information with us. This Privacy Policy tells you the types of information we collect when you use our sites or services, how we use that information, and the instances in which we share your information.

Your information will be transmitted to, held and processed by us in accordance with this privacy Policy.

**Ⅰ.WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT**

As set forth in more detail below, ShopSimple ("ShopSimple” or "We") collects personal information that you provide when using the ShopSimple website ("Site"). We collect two kinds of information related to you: (a) Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”); and (b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”).

**(a) Personally Identifiable Information:** PII includes any information that identifies you as person. We collect your PII when you choose to register with us or when you choose to participate in an interactive feature of our Site such as a review, survey or promotion. You may: (a) provide your real name, username, email address when registering with our Site or in connection with a contest entry; (b) provide certain demographic information about you (e.g., age, gender, shopping interests and preferences, etc.) when participating in a survey or poll; or (c) post a general comment and/or recommendation on our Sites. PII also includes any other information necessary for us to provide our services as well as credentials you provide us to link your Shopsimple account with third-party services such as Facebook and Twitter. If you If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts ("Third Party Account Information") may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Website is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you cannot be individually identified, and provide that information to our partners.

**(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** Non-PII is any information that does not identify you as a person including PII which has been rendered anonymous. We obtain non-PII either separately or together with your PII as described above. We collect certain non-PII from you when you access our Site including IP addresses and information relating to your browser, operating system, ISP, the third party website from which your visit originated and how you use our Sites such as the web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits.

**Ⅱ.HOW WE USE & SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED**

PII and Non-PII is used to provide, or improve our Site and Services to you and to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, better serve you and understand your needs, or is used in other ways naturally associated with the circumstances in which you provided the information.

We may disclose PII and Non-PII to:

1\. Our third party service providers who perform functions on our behalf in connection with the operation of the Site or Services e.g., providers who host and manage data, process credit card orders, deliver our merchandise, etc; 

2\. Participating sponsors to a program or promotion you enter through our Sites or Services; 

3\. Our parent company, subsidiaries or other affiliated companies (“affiliated companies”) for operational, marketing and promotional purposes; 4\. Co-promotional partners and others with whom we have marketing or other relationships; 

5.participating merchants where you consent at the time you submit PII to us when using the interactive features of our Sites such as surveys and reviews concerning our participating merchants; and 

6\. Our other users where you choose to publicly post reviews, comments or other information relating to products or services, communicate with other users via public forums (e.g., forums, message boards, bulletin boards, etc.). 

In addition, we use non-PII to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends carry out targeted promotional activities (see “Preference Based Advertising” below). We may use your non-PII by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from others to produce research reports and other information and data about online shopping for participating merchants and other customers, as well as media and other interested parties.

**Ⅲ. DIRECT MARKETING**  
We may contact you from time to time with a view to providing the latest information on our products and services / member program. If you do not wish to receive these updates, please login at http://www.shopsimple.com to unsubscribe. Alternatively, you may click the unsubscribe link as shown in our electronic promotional materials; or can write to us via e-mail to [hello@shopsimple.com](mailto:hello@shopsimple.com) or Rooms 05-15, 13A/F., South Tower, World Finance Centre, Harbour City, 17 Canton Road, Tsim Sha Tsui, Kowloon, Hong Kong or via calling at 00852-22060092. In accordance with the statutory requirements, we will honour your request not to use your Personal Data for the purposes of direct marketing. Unless otherwise instructed as per the above, we may use any of your Personal Data collected in the normal course of our business for direct marketing purposes.

**Ⅳ. ACCESSING PERSONAL DATA**  
You have full control and ability to correct or edit your Personal Data at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about direct marketing purpose, VIP promotional offers and new products and services or deletion of your VIP membership online account. You may request your right of access or right of correction by logging in at http://www.shopsimple.com. Alternatively, you can write to us via e-mail to [hello@shopsimple.com](mailto:hello@shopsimple.com) or via mail at Rooms 05-15, 13A/F., South Tower, World Finance Centre, Harbour City, 17 Canton Road, Tsim Sha Tsui, Kowloon, Hong Kong or via calling at 00852-22060092. We will, upon satisfying itself of the authenticity and validity of the access or correction request, make every endeavor to comply with and respond to the request within the period set by the statutory requirement. 

**V. COOKIES AND PREFERENCE BASED ADVERTISING**

**(a) Cookies and Web Beacons:** We automatically receive and store certain types of non-PII whenever you interact with us by using "cookies" and analogous technology. "Cookies" are small files that we place on your computer or your Web browser memory to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide convenience and other features to you. **It is important to note that the cookies that we use do not contain and are not tied to PII about you.**

You may be able to direct your internet browser not to allow cookies and you can delete existing cookies from your computer. Please note, however, some elements of our Sites will not function properly or be available to you. 

**(b) Preference Based Advertising:** We work with third parties, including advertising companies and website analysis firms, who use cookies to collect non-PII when you visit our Site and third party sites about your surfing activities. This non-PII, collected through cookies, is typically used by these third party advertising networks to: (a) serve you with advertisements, while on our Site and third party sites tailored to meet your preferences and likely interests; or (b) conduct market research and website analysis. If you do not wish to participate in this activity, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and follow the simple opt-out process.

A couple of important notes about this opt-out tool: (1) it includes all the advertising networks that ShopSimple works with, but also many that ShopSimple does not work with; and (2) it relies on cookies to ensure that a given advertising network does not collect information about you (“Opt-out Cookies”) – for a general explanation of how Opt-out Cookies work, please [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Therefore, if you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete these Opt-out Cookies from your computer, you will need to perform the opt-out task again.

**Ⅵ. SALE OF BUSINESS AND DISCLOSURE BY LAW**

**(a) Business Transactions:** We may disclose PII and Non-PII held by us: (a) to a prospective seller or actual seller of any business or assets we acquire; (b) if all or any of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case, PII and Non-PII may be one of the transferred assets.

**(b) Required disclosures:** We may disclose and use any PII or non-PII if we are required to do so by law, with respect to copyright and other intellectual property infringement claims, or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Sites, or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of our Sites’ users or the general public.

**Ⅶ. SECURITY OF INFORMATION**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We also use a secure server hosting location in the US, firewall protection, controlled access and encryption technology to protect your data. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your PII. In the unfortunate event that your personally identifiable information is compromised, we will notify you by e-mail to the last e-mail address you have provided us as soon as feasible under the circumstances (delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system, as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation).

**Ⅷ. YOUR OPTIONS & OPT-OUTS**

**(a) What Information Can I Access?** If you register as a Shopsimple member, you will typically have access to an account section that includes the registration information you previously provided which you can update or correct at any time. If there is any inaccurate information that you are not able to correct, just let us know. Furthermore, some information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical (e.g., information that is stored in our “back-up” systems) and certain legal constraints.

**(b) What Choices Do I Have (Opt-Out)?** You have many choices regarding how we use information about you, including: (1) To stop our emails, please email us at [hello@shopsimple.com](mailto:hello@shopsimple.com) ; (2) To opt-out of third party advertising, please email us at [hello@shopsimple.com](mailto:hello@shopsimple.com); And (3) as discussed above, the choices we offer you anytime you submit information through our Site or Services. 

**(c) You May Contact Us with Questions:** If you have any questions or concerns about privacy at Shopsimple, please contact us by [hello@shopsimple.com](mailto:hello@shopsimple.com) . 

**Ⅸ.CHILDREN**

We respect children’s privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13.On this website, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or using this site with the supervision of a parent or guardian.

**Ⅹ.REVISIONS**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time to reflect our changing business practices. We will provide you notice of any such changes by posting the new policy on our Sites or by email if the changes are material. We encourage you to review this privacy Notice from time to time, so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. Any questions, please contact us at [hello@shopsimple.com](mailto:hello@shopsimple.com).
